<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<file>
    <1>
        <informal>
            <female>
                Opt for a comfortable yet presentable outfit such as a well-fitted blouse or a casual dress. 
                You can pair it with jeans, trousers, or a skirt, depending on your personal style and preference. 
                Choose colors and patterns that suit your complexion and convey a professional yet relaxed vibe. 
                Avoid overly revealing or distracting clothing and opt for accessories that are simple and not overly flashy.
            </female>
            <male>
                For an informal setting, you can go for a collared shirt, polo shirt, or a neat t-shirt paired with 
                chinos, khakis, or dark-colored jeans. You can also consider wearing a casual blazer or cardigan to 
                add a touch of sophistication. Opt for clean and well-maintained footwear that complements your outfit. 
                Avoid wearing overly casual or wrinkled clothing, and ensure that your appearance is tidy and presentable.
            </male>
        </informal>
        <formal>
            <female>
                Choose a tailored blouse, button-down shirt, or a professional dress with a modest neckline and length. 
                Pair it with dress pants, a skirt, or a formal dress that exudes professionalism. Stick to neutral colors 
                or classic patterns, and avoid loud or flashy prints. Accessorize with simple and elegant jewelry, and ensure 
                that your hair and makeup are neat and professional.
            </female>
            <male>
                Opt for a crisp, well-fitted dress shirt paired with dress pants or tailored trousers. Consider wearing a 
                blazer or suit jacket to elevate your look further. Choose darker or neutral colors such as black, navy, or gray, 
                and ensure that your clothing is pressed and wrinkle-free. Complete your outfit with polished dress shoes and 
                minimal accessories.
            </male>
        </formal>
    </1>
    <2>
        <informal>
            <female>
                Feel free to use emojis that reflect your personality and the tone of the conversation. For instance, 
                you can use a smiley face 😊 to convey friendliness or happiness. If you find something amusing, you can use a 
                laughing face 😂. To show agreement or support, a thumbs-up 👍 can be an excellent choice. Remember to use emojis 
                sparingly and in appropriate contexts, keeping in mind the overall professionalism of the conversation.
            </female>
            <male>
                Feel free to use emojis that reflect your personality and the tone of the conversation. For instance, you can use a 
                smiley face 😊 to convey friendliness or happiness. If you find something amusing, you can use a laughing face 😂. 
                To show agreement or support, a thumbs-up 👍 can be an excellent choice. Remember to use emojis sparingly and in 
                appropriate contexts, keeping in mind the overall professionalism of the conversation.
            </male>
        </informal>
        <formal>
            <female>
                In a formal setting, it is advisable to use emojis sparingly. You can consider using a smiling face 🙂 at the end of 
                a message to add a touch of warmth or friendliness. An occasional thumbs-up 👍 can be used to acknowledge agreement 
                or approval. However, it's crucial to gauge the formality of the conversation and the expectations of the participants 
                to ensure that emojis are appropriate.
            </female>
            <male>
            </male>
        </formal>
    </2>
    <3>
        <informal>
            <female>
                When selecting a space for your formal online video meeting, choose a quiet and dedicated room where you can control 
                background noise and minimize distractions. Opt for a clean and professional-looking background, such as a blank wall 
                or a bookshelf with neatly arranged books. Ensure that the lighting is sufficient, with your face well-illuminated and 
                clearly visible to other participants. Consider using a professional virtual background if necessary, ensuring it is 
                appropriate and does not cause distractions.
            </female>
            <male>
                When selecting a space for your formal online video meeting, choose a quiet and dedicated room where you can control 
                background noise and minimize distractions. Opt for a clean and professional-looking background, such as a blank wall 
                or a bookshelf with neatly arranged books. Ensure that the lighting is sufficient, with your face well-illuminated and 
                clearly visible to other participants. Consider using a professional virtual background if necessary, ensuring it is 
                appropriate and does not cause distractions.
            </male>
        </informal>
        <formal>
            <female>
                In an informal online video meeting, choose a comfortable and inviting space that reflects a relaxed atmosphere. This 
                could be a living room, home office, or any area where you can feel at ease. Ensure that the background is clean and 
                visually appealing, avoiding any distracting elements. Consider adding personal touches to the background, such as 
                tasteful decorations or artwork, to add warmth and personality. Pay attention to lighting to ensure your face is well-lit 
                and clearly visible.
            </female>
            <male>
                For an informal online video meeting, find a space that is comfortable yet presentable. It could be a well-arranged home 
                office, a cozy corner of a room, or any area where you can engage in a relaxed conversation. Keep the background clean 
                and free from clutter, ensuring there are no distracting elements. Use appropriate lighting to ensure your face is well-lit 
                and visible. Consider adding some personal touches to the background, such as plants or artwork, to create a pleasant and 
                inviting atmosphere.
            </male>
        </formal>
    </3>
</file>